NewsLab turns a research plan into a controlled, browser-based news-feed study.
Researchers configure assignment, sample targets, consent, completion, and
condition-specific feed controls in one experiment workspace.
Articles become approved content sets, with direct control
over the sequence delivered to each condition.
Optional AI providers can propose article variants.
Every result enters a side-by-side human review before approval.
Participants enter through study-specific consent, then continue into
the experience assigned to their condition.
The responsive feed supports scrolling, article views, and
like, share, or save controls while recording each interaction.
The configured survey follows naturally, supporting Likert, choice,
and optional free-text questions.
Back in the researcher workspace, participant and session
summaries show progress while keeping preview records separate.
Finally, NewsLab exports events, participants, exposures, and survey
responses as structured CSV files with a data
dictionary. Researchers define the questions;
NewsLab runs the workflow.